Okay so let's run down some headlines. Hamas rejects talks over captives until genocidal war
ends. Israel is now doing actual executions in the street of people on their knees and we have
yet to see any true evidence of them actually smoting out Hamas. At this point what bargaining
chips are there to stop this genocide that is clearly not even about Hamas? We're all over here
like is it a boycott? Do we talk to our representatives? How do we stop this? I would
hope saving Israeli lives would be the first way but clearly we see that that has not been the
priority. France to impose sanctions on extremist Israeli settlers. Apparently Britain said the
same thing. Sanctions? Sanctions? These people need to be put under a jail. They are literally stealing
people's homes and killing them. Calling for a ceasefire is an anti-semitic demand that Jews
endorse our own genocide. This is an actual title of an op-ed in Newsweek. This is also complete and
absolute nonsense. Anytime you see something like this this is propaganda to try to make you think
that somehow peace is harmful to Jewish people in Israel. The fact that Newsweek published this
seriously lets us know that we have yet another information source that is questionable. This
perpetuates the faulty ideology that Palestinians are like orcs in the Tolkien universe. That they're
just bloodthirsty terrorists that are unsatiated when they very clearly said we just want freedom.
Platforming an article that says that they're afraid of a theoretical genocide when there's an
actual genocide happening of people says everything about whose lives matter.